GÖKSEL ÖZKAZANÇ



Contact

Address:

Dr.-Carlo-Schmid Straße 114 90491 Nürnberg/Germany

Phone:

(+49) 15737809964

Email:

goksel_ozkazanc_08@hotmail.com

Date of Birth:

15.04.1991

Languages

Turkish – Native English – B2 German – A2

Summary

During my 5 years of engineering experience, I worked in several firms in different roles. But since my childhood, I have had a big passion for information technologies. With the web design course which I attended in 2017-2018 and realized my special interest in web development, especially in the front-end development area. Thus, I took online courses that include HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Jquery, BootStrap4, WordPress. Since then, I am enhancing myself by having online courses, creating my own blog (www.gokselozkazanc.com), making practices, reading, and learning continuously. Therefore, I am looking for an opportunity to gain experience and to go on my career in the front-end development field.

Experience

Civil Engineer

03/2019 - 09/2020

TEIAS (Turkish Electricity Transmission Company) Ankara, Turkey

- Controlling and approving monthly progress payments reports that are prepared by subcontractors
- Controlling, calculating and approving quantity surveys that are prepared by subcontractors.
- Site selection and assessment based on structural regulations for prospective transformer stations

Technical Office Chief

05/2017 - 02/2018

Bilsezer Construction Co. Ltd Bursa, Turkey

- Preparing monthly progress payment reports
- Making all necessary calculations for quantity surveys
- Estimating the cost of materials and equipment.
- Following-up the schedules and informing the project manager in case of deviation from plans
- Comparing quantity survey quotes with the actual implemented work to prepare the Subcontractor Interim Payment.
- Preparing final progress payment reports

Site Manager

10/2016 - 05/2017

Robert Bosch Gmbh Turkey Bursa, Turkey

- Managing site activities and co-ordinating multi-disciplinary construction work
- Supervising and managing own site teams and subcontractors
- Monitoring of day to day activities
- Controlling, calculating and approving monthly progress payment reports prepared by subcontractors
- Making all necessary calculations for quantity surveys
- Providing technical advice and solving problems on-site
- Planning & scheduling of site works

Experience

Site Manager 08/2016 - 10/2016

Z-A Construction Co. Ltd. Bursa, Turkey

- Managing of all over site activities
- Supervising of day to day activities of the site construction works
- Supervising and managing of own site teams and subcontractors
- Preparing monthly progress payment reports.
- Making all necessary calculations for quantity surveys
- Planning & scheduling of site works

Technical Office Civil Engineer

04/2016 - 07/2016

Maksem Construction Inc. Ain Benian, Algeria

- Preparing monthly progress payment reports
- Making all necessary calculations for quantity surveys
- Daily and weekly planning the site works
- Controlling the schedules and informing the project manager in case of deviation from plans.

Civil Site Engineer

11/2015 - 04/2016

Şems Building Audit Co. Ltd. Kocaeli, Turkey

- Supervising of day to day activities of the site construction works
- Performing quantity take-off
- Comparing structural drawings with architectural drawings and informing contractors and drawing teams if there are any conflict

Civil Site Engineer

06/2014 - 06/2015

Al-taş Building Audit Co. Ltd. Trabzon, Turkey

- Supervising of day to day activities of the site construction works
- Performing quantity take-off
- Comparing structural drawings with architectural drawings and informing contractors and drawing teams if there are any conflict

Education

Master of Engineering: Healthy and Sustainable Buildings - (02.2020 - ...)

Deggendorf Technology Institute, Deggendorf, Germany

Bachelor's Degree: **Civil Engineering** - (08.2013 – 06.2014) Karadeniz Technical University, Trabzon, Turkey, 2.94/4.00 GPA

Bachelor's Degree: Civil Engineering - (02.2012 – 08.2013)

Wroclaw Environmental and Life Sciences University Wroclaw, Poland (Erasmus)

Bachelor's Degree: Civil Engineering - (09.2009 – 02.2012)

Karadeniz Technical University, Trabzon, Turkey

High School - (09.2005 – 06.2009)

Hopa Anatolian High School, Artvin, Turkey, 79.67/100.00 GPA

Skill Highlights

Computer skills:

MS Excel, MS Word, MS PowerPoint, Autocad, GoogleSketchup – Very good knowledge Revit Structure, Revit Architecture – Good knowledge Photoshop – Basic knowledge

Web/Programming skills:

HTML, CSS – Good knowledge Git, JavaScript, Bootstrap4, JQuery, Photoshop – Basic knowledge

Hobbies

Coding, Gaming, Computing, Designing, Traveling, Swimming, Cycling, Trekking, Language learning, Playing chess, Reading, Fishing

References

Available upon request